http://www.cascadedesigns.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last modified: July 26, 2018
Introduction
Cascade Designs, Inc. ("Company" or "We") respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.
This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit any of the following websites: www.cascadedesigns.com, www.msrgear.com, www.msrglobalhealth.com, www.thermarest.com, www.platy.com, www.seallinegear.com, www.packtowl.com, thesummitregister.com, or any other website solely owned and operated by the Company (our "Websites"), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.
This policy applies to information we collect:
On our Websites
In e-mail, text, and other electronic messages between you and our Websites
Through mobile and desktop applications you download from our Websites, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and our Websites
When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
All other social media and third party applications
It does not apply to information collected by:
the Company offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on our Websites.
Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Websites. By accessing or using any of our Websites, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of any of our Websites after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.
Children Under the Age of 13
Our Websites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on our Websites. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on our Websites or on or through any of our Websites’ features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at:
4000 1st Avenue South Seattle, WA 98134
contact us
800.531.9531
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Websites, including information:
by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline ("personal information");
that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as location; and/or
about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Websites and usage details.
We collect this information:
Directly from you when you provide it to us.
Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies.
From third parties, for example, our business partners.
Information You Provide to Us.  The information we collect on or through our Websites may include:
Information that you provide by filling in forms on any of our Websites. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use one or more of our Websites, or posting material. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with any of our Websites.
Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
Details of transactions you carry out through one or more of our Websites and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Websites.
Your search queries on our Websites.
You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of our Websites, or transmitted to other users of our Websites or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of our Websites with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. All User Contributions transfer to the Company a worldwide, royalty free, right in perpetuity for the Company to use User Transmission however it sees fit.
Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.  As you navigate through and interact with our Websites, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including without limitation:
Details of your visits to our Websites, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on our Websites.
Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.
The information we collect automatically may include personal information or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Websites and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:
Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Websites according to your individual interests.
Speed up your searches.
Recognize you when you return to our Websites.
The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser; however, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Websites. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to any of our Websites.
Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Websites may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Websites. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
Without limitation, our Websites use one or more of the following cookies: DoubleClick, BlueKai, Index Exchange, AppNexus, eXelate, Turn inc., LiveRamp, Adobe Audience Manager, Netmining, Krux Digital, Drawbridge, Google Adwords Conversion Tracker, Facebook Custom Audience, Google Dynamic Remarketing, PowerReviews, Google Adwords User Lists, Typekit by Adobe, Google Tag Manager, Google Analytics, Crazy Egg, GA Audiences, Avant Metrics, Facebook Connect.
Google Analytics. We use Google Analytics Advertising, which include at least the following: Remarketing (see support.google.com/google-ads/answer/2453998); Google Display Network Impression Reporting; Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. To understand how Google Analytics collects and processes data, please see www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners; for Google’s general Privacy Policy see www.policies.google.com/privacy. If you wish to opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features we use, please visit the following site which lists Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout; additionally, you can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browner plugin.
Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Some content or applications, including advertisements, on our Websites are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Websites. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.
We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
How We Use Your Information. We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:
To present our Websites and our Websites’ contents to you.
To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
To notify you about changes to our Websites or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Websites.
In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
For any other purpose with your consent.
We may also use your information to contact you about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form). If you have opted to subscribe to any of our e-mail mailing lists, you may unsubscribe from any such list by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any e-mail received. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.
Disclosure of Your Information. We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.
We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:
To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Cascade Designs, Inc.'s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Cascade Designs, Inc. about our Websites users is among the assets transferred.
To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
With your consent.
We may also disclose your personal information:
To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Cascade Designs, Inc., our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:
Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt out by filling out our contact form.
Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your e-mail address used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt out by filling out our contact form.. If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions.
Targeted Advertising. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers' target-audience preferences, you can opt out by filling out our contact form.
We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's website.
Accessing and Correcting Your Information
You can review and change your personal information by logging into our Websites and visiting your account profile page.
If you delete your User Contributions from our Websites, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on our Websites, including User Contributions, is governed by our terms of use.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on our Websites home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you through a notice on our Websites home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.
Contact Information
To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:
4000 1st Avenue South Seattle, WA 98134
contact us
or via our toll-free number:
Myanmar (Burma)
Thank you for joining!
Please enter an email address and select a country.
Sign up for newsletter failed.
Click to subscribe to our mailing list.
Myanmar (Burma)
Please enter an email address and select a country.
Sign up for newsletter failed.
Close window
